tattomedia.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - About - Tatto Media

## Privacy Policy

Effective April 2009

Thank you for visiting the Tatto Media website located at www.tattomedia.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Tatto, Inc., a Delaware State corporation ("Tatto Media," "we" or "us"). Tatto Media is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors' personally identifiable information. We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) register on the Site to participate as a Publisher, Affiliate and/or Advertiser on the Tatto Media Network (as those terms are defined in the Tatto Media Terms and Conditions ("Terms and Conditions")). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to become a Publisher, Affiliate and/or Advertiser (collectively, "Tatto Media Member") and/or use the Site in any manner or form whatsoever. 

**Personally Identifiable Information.** We collect personally identifiable information on the Site when you attempt to register as a Tatto Media Member or otherwise choose to provide personally identifiable information to us. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This may include, but is not limited to: business entity name and/or title with the applicable business entity, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, fax number, bank account information (including, but not limited to, account number, routing number and bank location), and/or any other information requested on the applicable Tatto Media Member registration form. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, your bank account information shall be considered "Sensitive Information." 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**. We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the Site's pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage. 

To make certain that the Ads (as that term is defined in the Terms and Conditions) served to Publisher websites by Tatto Media are targeted correctly, Publisher websites in the Tatto Media Network must place Tatto Media - provided data tags on their websites. These tags are not personally identifiable nor do they collect personally identifiable information. They are used to match visitor browsing behavior to a segment profile designated for targeting Ads to visitors on the applicable Publisher website. 

**Cookies.** To enhance your experience with the Site, we use "cookies." Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. You may set your browser to warn you that cookies are in use, or to block the use of cookies. Most browsers are set to accept cookies. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, certain uses of the Site may require you to go to your browser user preferences to enable cookies. Each browser is different, so check the ''Help'' menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. 

**Use of Information.** We use your personally identifiable information: (a) to send you information regarding Tatto Media and/or the Tatto Media Network, and your participation therein; (b) to operate the Tatto Media Network; (c) to track your compliance with the Terms and Conditions, the Tatto Media Publisher Agreement, Tatto Media Affiliate Agreement and/or Tatto Media Advertiser Agreement; and (d) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Tatto Media Network and request for information regarding Tatto Media products and/or services. 

**Information Sharing.** As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, Tatto Media will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Tatto Media may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services in connection with your participation in the Tatto Media Network such as billing, delivery and payouts. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by Tatto Media. 

Further, Tatto Media reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information: (a) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (b) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Tatto Media's business, assets or stock; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, the Terms and Conditions, the Tatto Media Publisher Agreement, Tatto Media Affiliate Agreement and/or Tatto Media Advertiser Agreement; (d) in the case of a dispute between you and a Publisher, Affiliate and/or Advertiser, as applicable; or (e) where Tatto Media determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Tatto Media and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Tatto Media from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

**Third Party Links.** The Site may contain links to third-party websites ("Third Party Websites"). Please be aware that Tatto Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site. Minors. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. Tatto Media will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If Tatto Media obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Security. We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users' information. When users submit personally identifiable information at the Site, their personally identifiable information is protected both online and offline. When our registration process asks users to submit Sensitive Information (such as bank account information), and when we transmit such Sensitive Information, that Sensitive Information is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we protect all other user information online and offline. The servers that we store personally identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information under our control. Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personally identifiable information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and third party agents, that need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personally identifiable information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. Deleting and Updating Your Information. If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you, simply send your request via certified mail to: Tatto Media, 10 High Street, Suite 900, Boston, MA 02111. You may also send your request via e-mail to: info@tattomedia.com. 

We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Opting Out of Receiving E-mail.** You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding Tatto Media by following the instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at optout@tattomedia.com. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your participation in the Tatto Media Network, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. 

**Notification of Changes.** Tatto Media reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Site explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes. 

**Contact Us.** If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at [legal@tattomedia.com](mailto:legal@tattomedia.com).
